[
   {
      "question": "In distributed system, each processor has its own ___________",
      "correct_answer": "c",
      "answers": [
         "a) local memory",
         "b) clock",
         "c) both local memory and clock",
         "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "If one site fails in distributed system then ___________",
      "correct_answer": "a",
      "answers": [
         "a) the remaining sites can continue operating",
         "b) all the sites will stop working",
         "c) directly connected sites will stop working",
         "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "Network operating system runs on ___________",
      "correct_answer": "a",
      "answers": [
         "a) server",
         "b) every system in the network",
         "c) both server and every system in the network",
         "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "Which technique is based on compile-time program transformation for accessing remote data in a distributed-memory parallel system?",
      "correct_answer": "b",
      "answers": [
         "a) cache coherence scheme",
         "b) computation migration",
         "c) remote procedure call",
         "d) message passing"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "Logical extension of computation migration is ___________",
      "correct_answer": "a",
      "answers": [
         "a) process migration",
         "b) system migration",
         "c) thread migration",
         "d) data migration"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "Processes on the remote systems are identified by ___________",
      "correct_answer": "b",
      "answers": [
         "a) host ID",
         "b) host name and identifier",
         "c) identifier",
         "d) process ID"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "Which routing technique is used in a distributed system?",
      "correct_answer": "d",
      "answers": [
         "a) fixed routing",
         "b) virtual routing",
         "c) dynamic routing",
         "d) all of the mentioned"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "In distributed systems, link and site failure is detected by ___________",
      "correct_answer": "b",
      "answers": [
         "a) polling",
         "b) handshaking",
         "c) token passing",
         "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "The capability of a system to adapt the increased service load is called ___________",
      "correct_answer": "a",
      "answers": [
         "a) scalability",
         "b) tolerance",
         "c) capacity",
         "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": ". Internet provides _______ for remote login.",
      "correct_answer": "a",
      "answers": [
         "a) telnet",
         "b) http",
         "c) ftp",
         "d) rpc"
      ]
   },
   {
      "question": "In distributed system, each processor has its own ___________",
      "correct_answer": "c",
      "answers": [
         "a) local memory",
         "b) clock",
         "c) both local memory and clock",
         "d) none of the mentioned"
      ]
   }
]